<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>House Over the Hill</title>
    <link>http://github.com/averagegrod/averagegrod.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on House Over the Hill</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 14:47:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://github.com/averagegrod/averagegrod.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>There will be cake!</title>
      <link>http://github.com/averagegrod/averagegrod.github.io/post/HappyBirthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 14:47:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://github.com/averagegrod/averagegrod.github.io/post/HappyBirthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another year.
Another blog. At least thats how I seem to operate. Going in I&amp;rsquo;d always say that I&amp;rsquo;m more committed to my current project than my previous one but  ironically each blog lives a shorter life than it&amp;rsquo;s predecessor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I might have commitment issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if there is anything in this world I am committed to it&amp;rsquo;s my kids. So this is going to be for them. More likely it will be about them. In fact, in an attempt to get off on the right foot, I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest. This is FOR me. It will be ABOUT them. Someday they&amp;rsquo;ll move on and I&amp;rsquo;ll still have this. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve got the honest part out of the way let me lie to you. Or at least warn you that I might in the future. Or at least embelish. Yep. My intention is to use this platform to capture things as I want to remember them. My kids are fun. They are awesome. Sometimes they are boring. Everything I post will be rooted in truth unless otherwise noted. Somethings may be enhanced for comedic effect. You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned. Walk away. Or don&amp;rsquo;t. I don&amp;rsquo;t care either way but you might find yourself entertained by these creatures. I know I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to honesty. I did offer you cake didn&amp;rsquo;t I? Birthday cake seems appropriate as this is the birth of the blog. I made the pictured &amp;ldquo;cake&amp;rdquo; at the request of my daughter for her tenth birthday. I baked her a rainbow cake a few years prior and figured this would be just as easy. They are simple in concept but do require a lot of time or a big oven and lots of pans. Take two boxes of cake mix, divide the batter up into six bowls, food coloring, bake all six different colors, layer them, frost them, eat them. SIMPLE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confession time. I totally botched it this time. I played dumb because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to correct the situation and also because I am a man so I am never wrong. I baked them according to the time listed for cupcakes. I kept them in the oven a lot longer than the incorrect directions said to be about a third of the time shy of what they require. This left me with a very squishy unstable &amp;ldquo;cake&amp;rdquo; and a look of suprised confusion on my face. My wife still doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what is wrong with our oven or why it doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to bake my cakes properly. I did my best. We bought cup cakes. She had a good time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emma, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this now I hope you are smiling. I love you. I owe you a cake.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>